say. Hmm, does that mean you're one of the straw hats? That's right, bro! He totally is! I was
expecting all of the straw hat crew to be really strong, but this one's not at all! Yeah, he's a
complete weakling! What a joke! Mind your own damn business! You've got some guts trying to take
back the money all by yourself, but I'm afraid I can't let you have it. Give it back! We
need the money to fix the berry! Her scars are deep! That's our money!
It's to heal her wounds, understand me? You can't have it! Give it back to me right now!
Rescuing our friend! Raid on the Frankie house!
What are you so worked up about? Seems like you love your ship quite a bit.
No matter. Whatever condition she's in, this money belongs to us now. Understand? Damn you!
Unfortunately, in this world, stealing from pirates isn't really seen as a crime. Besides,
this is probably dirty money you swiped somewhere along the way here. Just let us have it. Maybe you could beg the Navy for help. Nah, they'd just arrest you.
Too bad for Straw Hat Luffy. He's got himself a useless crony who can't even handle the simple task of guarding a little money. Such a shame.
All right, boys. Show them all the hospitalities of the Frankie house while I'm gone. No time like the present to start shopping with this pile of money. Man, this is gonna be great. Hold it! Sensual attack! Exploding star!
Remember my name, long-nosed boy. It's Frankie. If you wanna leave this city alive, I'd suggest you never cross me.
You call this little kid's toy a weapon? See you later, long-nosed. Thanks again for the 200 million berries. No! Wait! Give it back! Give back the berry! You hear me? Give it back!
Give it back!
No! Give it back!
Get! Get!
Back!
No! Please!
Get me back!
I need to wait here until Robin comes back.
If I march in with the others right now, I'll just be in the way.
It'll be scary, too.
For now, the best thing I can do is stay here, guard the money, and protect the Mary.
Don't let me down, guys. I'm counting on you.
Stop! Stop!
If I remember correctly, this is the place Nami was talking about.
Look, this is the Backstreet Shopping District.
You go up this canal, turn, then here. Usopp is right here.
Got it.
Nami, where are those dismantlers you mentioned? The Frankie family. Show me.
Hey, Usopp!
I guess he left.
Are you sure? Maybe you just screwed up the directions.
I'm not you, moron! Shut your hole!
Usopp!
What'd you say?
Look at this!
It's blood! See?
That idiot. I guess he walked off somewhere on his own.
Wait, you don't think that he...
Usopp, no.
Huh?
It fell off!
Luffy!
Go out!
Come on, girl!
What are you doing? And where the hell did you fall from?
The shipyard. I was trying to jump around like that carpenter to look for Usopp.
Are you alright?
Yeah.
Oh, that's right! I almost forgot! We've got a terrible problem! Usopp was abducted and so is the money!
We know. That's why we're here. Come on. We were just about to head over to the hideout of the guys that did it.
I'll bet that's where we'll find Usopp and the money.
Maybe he felt responsible about what happened and went to settle the matter with the Frankie family on his own.
Alright then. We'll be leaving now.
That man is seriously stubborn. It's infuriating.
We don't even know if he has it or not, yet they keep sending me out here over and over again.
I wish those people would put themselves in my shoes for once.
It's Khalifa.
Well, come in.
You must be worn out, sir. Would you like something to drink?
I would, thank you.
Maybe some tea.
I've already prepared it.
Well, I'd expect nothing less from you.
Thank you. I'm grateful.
Poor Mr. Corgi is always so angry when he leaves, isn't he?
What in the world does he come here to talk about?
Oh, that.
Those he represents want something I have, and they keep making various offers.
It must be something of great importance then, isn't it?
Well, maybe so, though I always deny knowing anything about it.
They really are tiresome people.
They're all in it.
Well, we're in it, isn't it?
Is he breathing, Chopper?
He's unconscious, but...
Yes, he's breathing.
He'll live.
I can save him.
You wait out here for us.
Okay, Usopp.
We're going to go level that stupid house to the ground.
Hey, somebody go buy some more food!
Yeah, we've got the money.
Get some more booze while you're at it.
When it comes to painting, I'm in a league of my own.
So what do you think?
My goggles!
You got them back from that creep for me!
Thank you so much!
Well, let me tell you about the time that I, Usopp, bravely fought off vicious sea kings in the comm belt, young chopper.
Big ones too!
Huge!
Be warned!
Captain Usopp has an army!
8,000 men!
It took all the money!
How can I face the others now, dummy?
All right, guys, it's time to kick their asses!
All of them!
That's it! Show them!
Looks like you lose this round!
Losers get to go pick up more booze!
Buy all the food they have in the shop too!
It's not like we don't have the money!
Be right back!
And when I am, I'm gonna win every hand!
Just you wait!
Hmm?
Ah!
What was that?
What happened?
Ah!
Who the hell are those guys?
You jerks!
You got a death wish?
Hmm!
I recognize them!
Ah!
Ha!
tractor it tight!
Ah!
Ha, ha, ha, but since you're here,
we might as well take those big bounties
you've got on your heads.
He's the captain of that long-nosed weakling
we took care of earlier.
With that pitiful excuse for a pirate on his crew,
he can't possibly be that strong.
Let's go.
Come on, shrimp.
Now come go!
What do you think you're doing?
Ha, ha, ha, are you punching him?
Not even a bombardment for battleship cannons
can put a den in that armor.
Ha, ha, ha, what a joke.
If you're just gonna play around,
then I'll go ahead and end this right now.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha.
Ha!
And cannon!
He punched a hole right through it.
Hey! Hold on. Wait a second, you guys. Let's talk about this first.
Okay. Guys. Okay, guys. Fire the cannons.
Woo-hoo!
Now Three-Sword Style. Karasuma.
Raven Hunt.
What? Impossible! Those cannonballs are made of iron!
Whoa!
The cannons too!
Holy crap! These guys are seriously bad news!
Let's get out of here! Everyone run for the back door!
You guys started this fight. It's kind of pathetic to run from it like cowards.
Party table kick court!
We can't make it to the back door! Windows! Use the windows!
Rumble!
More points!
Live to go!
You guys! It-it's the money, right? You-I just want the money back!
The 200 Million Berries the Long Nose Guy had. Is that it?
I'm sorry to be the one to tell you, but that pile of money isn't here anymore.
Frankie, the family boss, took it all and went on a shopping spree.
And since he's buying something on the black market,
we don't have any idea where he might be or even how to find him.
So no matter how much of a rampage you go on,
that $200 million won't be coming back.
So why don't you...
Shut up. That's enough out of you.
This has nothing to do with the money.
Damn straight. It's too late for that.
Not even your bones will be left when we're done.
Not even our bones?
What's the matter with you acting like a bunch of cowards?
We're the Frankie family.
We're the ones who do all the bone breaking around here.
Got it? Never forget who you are.
Okay, brothers, let's show them the specialty of the Frankie house.
Now, fire the anything shot cannon!
Here they come! Attack!
Hold on up! Keep firing till there's nothing left to shoot!
Come on! There's only four of them!
What was that? Fireworks?
Sounds like it's coming from out toward the Frankie house.
Them again?
What trouble are they up to this time?
I know, right?
Hey, quiet! They're gonna hear us!
Oh, boy. Sounds like they're getting a little carried away.
When those boys party. They really don't show any restraint, now do they?
No big deal. It's not like they do it all the time. It's a nice day.
Ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha, ha!
Should we go after Frankie?
And start looking where?
Oh man, looks like these idiots really didn't know where he took the money.
And if we do find him, if he spent it, then there's no getting it back.
What now? Even if we wait around for him, he may not be back for quite a while.
Okay, the first aid treatment is all done. We need to take him back on a stretcher so I could use some help over here!
Hanging around here won't do any good. Let's head back to the ship for now. We left Nami there all by herself.
And Robin's still missing. The ship's a problem too.
Yeah.
Hey, Luffy!
I've made a decision.
Huh?
About the ship.
It's time to part ways with the Mary. We'll say goodbye to her here.
Thank you.
See you next time.
One Piece! Big fight under the moon!
The pirate flag flutters with sorrow!
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!